Luke Forsyth

Various freelance positions - Joiner, Workshop Management, Site Management - Hanson Interiors

Grimsby DN36 lukeforsyth66_58x@indeedemail.com 07874125847

Experienced Manager in the Construction Industry with a Joinery trade background. I have experience in Site and Project Management in a sub-contract environment - Joinery and Interiors, and in running my own Shop Fitting businesses delivering projects and packages up to £1M in value across various sectors including; Retail, Student Accommodation, Commercial and Residential.

SALARY: Negotiable

PREFERRED LOCATION: Flexible with travel

Work Experience

Various freelance positions - Joiner, Workshop Management, Site Management

Hanson Interiors August 2017 to Present

Private Domestic Work Gray & Sons Shopfitting LTD

Position: Various freelance positions - Joiner, Workshop Management, Site Management

Projects: Various; high-spec kitchens, extensions, building work, interiors, bedrooms, shop fitting, banks refurbs. Project Values £15K-£80K

Various Freelance Positions

2017 to Present

Innovate & Design UK Limited 2016 - 2017

Joinery Director/Project Manager

Innovate & Design UK Limited November 2016 to August 2017

Project: Refurbishing high street banks including; joinery, dry lining and management of mechanical aspects. Project Values £25K-£165K packages typically involved all 1st and 2nd fix works joinery related including kitchens and bedrooms.

Duties: Managing multiple sites nationally where time management was paramount. Managing sub-contractors, H&S and RAMS. Organised site labour nationally and costed accordingly.

Owner/Contracts Manager (Joinery Installations)

New Image Joinery Ltd June 2014 to November 2016 Project: Refurbishing high street banks including; joinery, dry lining and management of mechanical aspects. Project Values £25K-£165K packages typically involved all 1st and 2nd fix works joinery related including kitchens and bedrooms.

Duties: Negotiated works, contracts (predominantly IC11 and MC11) and programmes. Managing multiple sites nationally where time management was paramount. Managing sub-contractors, H&S and RAMS. Organised site labour nationally and costed accordingly.

New Image Joinery Ltd 2014 to 2016

Joinery Supervisor

AMJAC Ltd

December 2011 to June 2014

Projects: Predominantly working for large contractors in the South i.e. Berkeley First, Berkeley Homes, McLaren Construction on multi-million pound sites developing student accommodation for universities and schools. Package Values £30K- £500K

Duties: Started as a joiner temporarily but soon moved into supervision and site management. Responsibilities included; management of H&S, RAMS, sub-contractors management, PC and client relations for all 1st and 2nd fix joinery and kitchens/bedrooms on sites. This included dry lining, stud work, bulkheads, dpm and access hatches.

AMJAC Ltd 2011 to 2014

NJ Richards Ltd June 2007 to December 2011

Position: Shop Fitting Joiner

Projects: Various shop fitting projects, clients included; H&M, Louis Vuitton, Zara across Europe. Values up to £1M

Duties: Company oversaw all works involved in shop fitting including; dry lining, joinery and M&E. Part of a small team of joiners working to very high standards to ensure the fits ran smoothly, dry lining, grid ceilings, bulkheads and all other joinery related tasks. Working long hours including nights to ensure handover was a success.

NJ Richards Ltd 2007 to 2011

Education

A-Level or equivalent